[Music]
iFit did a full
crazy thinking about the way I want did
the Heart Break Change
Me Maybe but look at where I ended up
I'm all good already so moved on it's
scary I'm not where you left me at
all so if you don't want to see me
dancing with
somebody if you never believe that
anything can stop
me don't show up don't come out don't
stop caring about me now walk away
you know how don't startop caring about
me now aren't you the guy who tried to
hurt me with the word goodbye though it
took some time to so I you I'm better on
the other side I'm all good already so
moved on it's scary I'm not where you
left me at all
so if you don't want to see me dancing
with
somebody if you to believe that anything
stop
me don't show up don't come out don't
startop caring about me now walk away
you know how don't startop caring about
me now
[Music]
I'm not where you left me at
all so if you don't want to see me
dancing with
somebody if you want to believe that
anything could stop me
don't show up don't show up don't come
out don't come out don't stop caring
about me now about me now walk away walk
away you know how you know how don't
stop caring about me